<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Hacker Tracker</string>
    <string name="action_share">Share</string>

    <!-- navigation drawer item labels  -->

    <string-array name="filter_types">
        <item>@string/official</item>
        <item>@string/speakers</item>
        <item>@string/skytalks</item>
        <item>@string/events</item>
        <item>@string/villages</item>
        <item>@string/kids</item>
        <item>@string/labs</item>
        <item>@string/breaks</item>
        <item>@string/contests</item>
        <item>@string/parties</item>
        <item>@string/demo_labs</item>
        <item>@string/workshops</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="official">DEFCON</string>
    <string name="speakers">Speakers</string>
    <string name="contests">Contests</string>
    <string name="demo_labs">Demo Labs</string>
    <string name="villages">Villages</string>
    <string name="labs">Labs</string>
    <string name="breaks">Break</string>
    <string name="events">Events</string>
    <string name="parties">Parties</string>
    <string name="kids">Kids</string>
    <string name="skytalks">Skytalks</string>
    <string name="workshops">Workshops</string>



    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="schedule">Schedule</string>
    <string name="map">Maps</string>


    <string name="badges">Badges &amp; Admission</string>
    <string name="wifi">DEF CON WiFi</string>
    <string name="radio">DEF CON Radio</string>


    <string name="no_updates">Your schedule is up to date! :)</string>
    <string name="schedule_finished">Schedule sync complete</string>
    <string name="tba">TBA</string>
    <string name="save">Save</string>

    <string name="workshop_info_text">
        Workshop registration was held online July 5th. There is no on-site registration, signup sheet, and all seats (including standby) are sold out.\n\n
        For more information on the workshops, please visit the DEF CON website.\n\n
        Pre-registration will be online again for DEF CON 26.
    </string>

    <string name="badges_description">
        DEF CON regular badge pricing is $260, cash only, at the DEF CON registration area. See map for directions to registration area.
        \n\nDEF CON does not offer pre-registration.
        \n\nBadges go on sale 6AM Thursday morning! Welcome to LineCon! Bring a drink (and/or coffee), make some friends, and enjoy the ride. :)
    </string>

    <string name="wifi_description"><![CDATA[
        Caesars Palace rooms will give you access to wifi for up to two devices.\n\n
        DEF CON WiFi registration information will be available at http://wifireg.defcon.org.\n\n
        DEF CON is FULLY network-enabled. Now that we\'ve perfected the art of a stable hacker con network, we\'re ascending to a higher level - we\'re providing you a network that you feel SAFE in using! Since DEF CON 18 we\'re WPA2 encrypted over-the-air, with a direct trunk out to the Internet. No peer-to-peer, no sniffing, just straight to the net (and internal servers). We\'ll provide login credentials at Registration. We know the 3G airwaves will be saturated so we\'re putting our own cred on the line to give you a net that even we would put our own mobile phones on.\n\n
        If you\'re feeling frisky, we\'ll still have the traditional \"open\" network for you - bring your laptop (we\'d recommend a clean OS, fully patched—you know the procedure) because we don\'t police what happens on that net. Share & enjoy!
    ]]></string>

    <string name="radio_text">
        Music for Hacking. The DEF CON Year-Round Channel.\n\n
        Since 2013, SomaFM has provided the music for the DEF CON Chill room. That theme continues with SomaFM broadcasting this special year-round stream hosted by the DJs who entertain the DEF CON 24 chill room this year in Vegas.\n\n
        Check out http://somafm.com/defcon/ to listen online, or download the Android app here: https://somafm.com/mobile/android.html
    </string>

    <string-array name="faq_questions">
        <item>When and where is DEF CON 25?</item>
        <item>DEF CON is generally in the last week of July or first week of August in Las Vegas. DEF CON 25 will be held July 27–30, 2017, at Caesars Palace in Las Vegas. Many people arrive a day early, and many stay a day later. Again this year we will have some things running on Thursday.</item>
        <item>Is DEF CON 25 canceled?</item>
        <item>No.</item>
        <item>How much is admission?</item>
        <item>$260.00 USD, Cash for all four days. Everyone pays the same: The government, the media, the ‘well known hackers’, the unknown script kiddies. The only discount is for Goons and speakers, who get to work without paying for the privilege. We only accept cash - no checks, no money orders, no travelers checks. We don\'t want to be a target of any State or Federal fishing expeditions.</item>
        <item>Can I pre-register for DEF CON?</item>
        <item>No.</item>
        <item>How many people will be there?</item>
        <item>Last year we had more than 20,000 people at DEF CON! The last few years, attendance has been in the 15–19k range.</item>
        <item>How much do rooms at Caesars Palace cost, and how do I reserve a room?</item>
        <item>The DEF CON rate is available at the following hotels: Caesars Palace, Paris, Bally\'s, Flamingo and Quad. Check out the DEF CON 25 Venue page for all the details!</item>
        <item>I can\'t afford that.</item>
        <item>Try the Ride and Room sharing threads on the Forums.

            You may also want to visit your Local DEF CON Groups meeting and see who you might want to bunk up with. It\'s important to mention you should use good judgment when sharing a room and consider who is sleeping next to you and who has access to your belongings. That said, there are a lot of great people looking to save a buck or pinch a penny, good luck.</item>
        <item>Can I get a discount on DEF CON badges?</item>
        <item>DEF CON charges one price regardless of your social status or affiliation. Please know that we depend on attendee income to pay the costs of the conference and don\'t have sponsors to help defray the expenses.

We sometimes get requests for discounts [students, veterans, children], unfortunately we don\'t want to try and validate if you are a current student, look at your ID to determine your age, decode military discharge papers, etc.

If you really want to attend DEF CON for free then do something for the con.

You could:
Submit a CFP and be an accepted speaker or workshop instructor.
Work on a contest, event, or village.
Qualify for CTF/Contests that include entry.
Find a team to become a Goon newbie.
Contribute to content, or perform some entertainment.</item>
        <item>I need a letter of invite for my visa application, how do I get that?</item>
        <item>In most cases, DEF CON can send a signed letter of invite, usually within a few short business days once we have all the info. If you also require verification of housing, we can put you in touch with someone to help you get your hotel stay organized, let us know if you need that.

Along with your request, please email us the following to info(at)defcon(.)org

Name as is on passport:
Passport number:
Country of issue:
Date of issue:
Date of expiration:
Country of origin:</item>

        <item>How much is internet access in the rooms of Caesars Palace?</item>
        <item>We\'ll let you know soon. Internet access is available for free in the convention area.</item>
        <item>Is there a free network at DEF CON?</item>
        <item><![CDATA[Why yes, DEF CON is FULLY network-enabled. Now that we\'ve perfected the art of a stable hacker con network, we\'re ascending to a higher level - we\'re providing you a network that you feel SAFE in using! Since DEF CON 18 we\'re WPA2 encrypted over-the-air, with a direct trunk out to the Internet. No peer-to-peer, no sniffing, just straight to the net (and internal servers). We\'ll provide login credentials at Registration. We know the 3G airwaves will be saturated so we\'re putting our own cred on the line to give you a net that even we would put our own mobile phones on.

If you\'re feeling frisky, we\'ll still have the traditional "open" network for you - bring your laptop (we\'d recommend a clean OS, fully patched—you know the procedure) because we don\'t police what happens on that net. Share & enjoy!]]></item>
        <item>Will Caesars Palace allow free parking?</item>
        <item>Yes. You will be able to park for free regardless if you have a room at Caesars Palace.</item>
        <item>What about the smoking policy?</item>
        <item>Due to the Clean Air Act in Las Vegas, the Vendor Area, Speaking rooms, and Hallways will be completely non-smoking in order to comply with the law. The Hotel will have designated smoking areas clearly posted. There is a discussion about it on the DEF CON Forums here: https://forum.defcon.org/showthread.php?t=8200
Any news and info will likely be posted there.</item>
        <item>What is the age limit?</item>
        <item>People have brought children to DEF CON - it is not recommended to do this unless you are going to constantly supervise them. It is generally an ‘adult’ atmosphere (language, booze, et cetera). If you\'ve never been to DEF CON, you may want to refrain from bringing your children (unless they are demanding that you bring them). While there are no age limits, we have consistently cooperated with parents and/or private investigators who are looking for children that ‘ran away from home’ to go to DEF CON. You must be 18 years of age or older to reserve a hotel room and to check-in. A valid ID is required upon check-in. DEF CON 25 will have enforcement of the 21 or older rule in certain "private" parties with possible bouncers at the doors checking IDs. This is generally the rule in all areas where alcohol is being served. However, DEF CON does not take responsibility for anything potentially indecent or offensive your minor may witness or participate in. The underage attendee is the responsibility of his or her guardian or themselves. The presentations are open to all ages. Observation of contests as they take place on the contest floor is open to all ages. Competition in some contests may have age restrictions due to laws. There is plenty fun to be had without booze and gambling! There is a discussion regarding fun for those under 21 on the forums. https://forum.defcon.org/showthread.php?t=8232</item>
        <item>I want to speak, how do I give a talk?</item>
        <item>GREAT! We are looking for and give preference to: unique research, new tool releases, Ø-day attacks (with responsible disclosure), highly technical material, social commentaries, and ground breaking material of any kind. Want to screen a new hacking documentary or release research? Consider DEF CON. To submit a speech, read the Announcement and complete the DEF CON 25 Call for Papers Form: https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-25/dc-25-cfp-form.html CFP forms and questions should get mailed to: talks/at/defcon.org</item>
        <item>When does the CFP Close? Can I get an Extension?</item>
        <item>DEF CON 25 Call For Papers will close on May 1, 2017.</item>
        <item>How can I help or participate?</item>
        <item>DEF CON is not a spectator sport! Before the con, during, and after there are chances for you to get involved. Below is a list of this years contests and events. This list may not be complete so check the forums to see what people are up to. Go to the forums for more info on Contests and Events: https://forum.defcon.org/forum/defcon/dc25-official-unofficial-parties-social-gatherings-events-contests</item>
        <item>How do I become a Vendor?</item>
        <item>Keep an eye out for the Vendor registration opening. If you want a space in our vendor area, you need to apply. Because of limited space and our attempt to have a diversity of vendors, you may not be able to get a booth. It is wise to think of staffing issues - if you are one person do you want to spend your entire time behind a vendors booth?</item>
        <item>I\'m press, how do I sign up, why can\'t I get in for free (I\'m just doing my job)?</item>
        <item>Please check out the DEF CON 25 Press Registration page (opening soon) if you wish press credentials. Lots of people come to DEF CON and are doing their job; security professionals, federal agents, and the press. It wouldn\'t be fair to DEF CON attendees if we exempted one group from paying. If you are a major network and plan on doing a two minute piece showing all the people with blue hair, you probably shouldn\'t bother applying for a press pass - you won\'t get one. If you are a security writer or from a real publication please submit, and someone will respond with an answer.</item>
        <item>What should I bring to DEF CON?</item>
        <item>It depends on what you\'re going to do at DEF CON. This is discussed in quite some depth on the unofficial DC FAQ, as well as a thread in the DC Forums. You may want to bring fancy (or outrageously silly) clothes for the Black and White Balls, annual Friday and Saturday night events where everyone shows off nifty attire. SWAG is Always recommended, people LOVE to trade! You never know when or where a t-shirt with your .org will come in handy. Government SWAG is a hot commodity, however, DT wishes to pillage those goods first! Its generally a good idea if you are a pale geek to have some sunscreen at the top of your list. Other honorable mentions are: Blister preventions, Band-aids, Gel shoe inserts, Personal cooling devices, Pain relievers and antacids, Bottle openers, Personal voice recorders, water filters, and last but not least an Alibi.</item>
        <item>This FAQ didn\'t answer my questions, or was unclear, how can I get further information?</item>
        <item>There is a forum discussion thread in which you can ask follow up questions. https://forum.defcon.org/showthread.php?t=6845</item>
    </string-array>


    <string-array name="faq_questions_shmoo">
        <item>STREAMING</item>
        <item>Live streaming of ShmooCon 2018\'s talks:\n\nOne Track Mind (Friday) / Bring it On! (Saturday, Sunday)\nhttps://livestream.com/ShmooConTrack3\n\nBelay It! (Saturday, Sunday)\nhttps://livestream.com/ShmooConTrack2\n\nBuild It! (Saturday, Sunday)\nhttps://livestream.com/ShmooConTrack1</item>
        <item>TICKET PRICE </item>
        <item>All general admission tickets for ShmooCon 2018 will be sold for $150</item>
        <item>TICKET SALES</item>
        <item>Tickets for ShmooCon 2018 will be sold on Nov 1, Dec 1, and Dec 10, 2017 at noon, eastern time.  Be warned, tickets sell out very quickly.  Last year tickets sold out in just over 9 seconds (yes, you read that right) across the three rounds of sales.  These dates are subject to change so please keep an eye on our news page or follow us on twitter for updates.\n\nPlease read the rest of the information found on this page.  You should also take the time to familiarize yourself with the information on our registration page - http://shmoocon2.org/human-registration/</item>
        <item>BARCODES</item>
        <item>Everyone who purchases admission for ShmooCon will be issued a barcode.  Your barcode is extremely important.  It is your ticket into the con.\n\nAnyone over the age of 12 attending the con will need a barcode.\n\nShmooCon Mantra:\n\nThere will be many barcodes, but the one we send you is your own.\nYour barcode is your best friend.\nWithout it, you cannot get into the con.\nWithout the con, your barcode is useless.\nEach barcode can only be used once, so if you share it the first one in the door wins.</item>
        <item>CANCELLATION POLICY</item>
        <item>Firstly, just because you bought a ticket does not mean you’re entitled to a refund.\n\nBought a ticket and now you can’t make it to the con?  Give or sell your ticket to a friend, we don’t care!  Don’t have any friends?  Contact us and we may be able to lend you a friend for a day. (In other words, we may be able to work out a ticket exchange for you.)  If you’re still stuck in a bind and have a VERY good excuse, shoot us an email and we’ll try to work something out for you.\n\nAbsolutely no fees will be refunded after January 1, 2018.</item>
        <item>SECOND HAND SALES</item>
        <item>We know that this is a hot topic.  Let us first start by saying most of the feedback we get is that in general tickets are being sold to friends/co-workers/etc. at cost, or cost-plus (where plus equals a beer at the bar, $20 for my time, etc).  We’re alright with that.  Some tickets get donated to charity and auctioned off – we’re ok with that too.  Want to just give your ticket away to a poor college student or someone else – yup, that’s great as well.\n\nIf you’re looking for a legitimate way to sell your extra ticket to a stranger – contact us.  We usually have a waiting list and as long as you are willing to sell the ticket at cost, we will help you sell it.   Transactions managed this way also protect the buyer as we will reissue the barcode to the new purchaser.\n\nUnfortunately, every year some tickets do end up on eBay or being resold via other avenues often at 2-3 times cost.  We don’t approve of these tickets being sold for undeserved profit.  From what we can determine, this type of activity is a small percentage of overall sales and because of that we’ve pretty much chosen a monitor but do nothing approach.   If we see the volume increasing, we may take action but for now we’re of the mind to let the community police these sales.  The best way to stop these kinds of sales from happening?  Don’t buy them and encourage your friends to do the same.\n\nSome things to note if you are considering purchasing a ticket directly from someone you don’t know:\n\nWe don’t approve of it.\nWe won’t get involved.\nYou risk that barcode being sold again and our rules are the first one to the door wins.\nAnd yes.  Sometimes bad things happen.  One poor guy showed up with a code purchased on eBay and it was bad at the door.  If memory serves it was actually a barcode from the year prior.  Could this have been done in error? Maybe…and we’re not sure how it got resolved but he wasn’t let into the con with the bad barcode.\n\nIn summary – BUYING TICKETS FROM OTHERS IS DONE AT YOUR OWN RISK.</item>
        <item>LAST BUT NOT LEAST</item>
        <item>ShmooCon supports the free and open exchange of information.\n\nWe are proud to have attendees with unique and diverse viewpoints on just about any topic.  We want to foster the exchange of ideas among attendees and think the community benefits from inclusiveness.  To that end, we are committed to providing a friendly, lively, and welcoming environment for all.\n\nFor your part, please be awesome to one another.\n\nWhat is awesome?  In the most simplest terms it means tolerance and respect.  Be helpful, be kind, be responsible.  It makes the experience better for everyone.  Marginalization, intimidation, and harassment are examples of what is not awesome and will be addressed accordingly.\n\nIf someone is not being awesome to you or you see someone not being awesome, please tell a staff member or contact us at security@shmoocon.org (active and monitored 24/7 for the duration of the conference). If you, yourself, are not being awesome, be aware that the consequences are yours to bear.  This may include being asked to leave the conference without refund and/or dealing with the proper authorities should it be warranted.\n\nWe value our attendees, speakers, and all our volunteers – they (you!) are why we come together every year and we hope you will work with us to keep ShmooCon amazing.</item>
        <item>QUESTIONS</item>
        <item>All questions should be directed here - info@shmoocon.org.  Please include the name of your favorite astronaut.</item>
        <item>DIRECTIONS FROM HOTEL ROOM BLOCK</item>
        <item>The ShmooCon rate for a single/double room is $189/night.  You can book your reservation on our block by using the GROUP code SHMOO.  If you book a room outside of our block, please let us know (we only need your reservation id and last name), so that we can still get credit towards our room commitment.</item>
        <item>METRO DIRECTIONS</item>
        <item>Dupont Circle Metro Station (Red Line)\nExit at the north end of the station to Q Street. Walk four blocks north on Connecticut Avenue to the hotel. Fares vary from $1.85 depending on distance traveled. Additional information is available from Washington Metro.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="faq_questions_hw">
        <item>When and where is HackWest?</item>
        <item>Salt Lake City Utah, at the Salt Palace Convention Center. March 21-23, 2018.</item>
        <item>How much is admission?</item>
        <item>$100</item>
        <item>Where can I get more information?</item>
        <item>https://hackwest.org</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="faq_questions_l1">
        <item>When and where is LayerOne?</item>
        <item>LayerOne 2018 will be held at the Pasadena Hilton in Pasadena, CA on May 25-27, 2018. If you\'re not attending a training, the effective conference dates are May 26-27, 2018. For those of you flying in, the closest airport is the Hollywood/Burbank (Bob Hope) International Airport (BUR).</item>
        <item>How much is admission?</item>
        <item>$120</item>
        <item>Where can I get more information?</item>
        <item>https://layerone.org</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="faq_questions_bsidesorl">
        <item>When and where is BSides Orlando?</item>
        <item>B-Sides Orlando will be held at Full Sail University at the Full Sail Live Venue – 141 University Park Dr, Winter Park, FL 32792</item>
        <item>How much is admission?</item>
        <item>Attendee tickets are $20. You can get them now at Eventbrite. Students are free. (Student ID required) Please considering purchasing attendee, silver, or gold tickets to help us continue to provide a great learning experience to students for free.\n\nhttps://www.eventbrite.com/e/security-b-sides-orlando-2018-tickets-41971150842</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="demo">DEMO</string>
    <string name="tool">TOOL</string>
    <string name="exploit">EXPLOIT</string>
    <string name="timestamp_full">%1$s, %2$s - %3$s</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="okay">Okay</string>
    <string name="notification_text">Starting soon in %1$s.</string>
    <string name="notification_updated">Details have been updated.</string>
    <string name="uber">Uber</string>
    <string name="tut_introduction"><![CDATA[Welcome to <h1><font>DEFCON 25</font></h1>]]></string>
    <string name="tut_location">DEF CON 25 will be held July 27–30, 2017, at Caesars Palace in Las Vegas.\n\nMany people arrive a day early, and many stay a day later. Again this year we will have some things running on Thursday.</string>
    <string name="tut_badge"></string>
    <string name="tut_workshop"></string>
    <string name="link_warning">External Link</string>
    <string name="link_message">Warning: external links can be dangerous. Are you sure you wish to open the following link?\n\n%1$s</string>
    <string name="open_link">Open Link</string>
    <string name="tut_hacker_jep"><![CDATA[Check out Hacker Jeopardy, it\'s definitely worth it.\n\nJust <font>don\'t fuck it up.</font>]]></string>
    <string name="unbookmark">Unbookmark</string>
    <string name="bookmark">Bookmark</string>
    <string name="empty_text">No further information available.\nYou\'ll have to look somewhere else.</string>
    <string name="details">Details</string>
    <string name="information">Information</string>
    <string name="nav_home">Home</string>


    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="map_uber">Maps &amp; Uber</string>
    <string name="partners_vendors">Partners &amp; Vendors</string>
    <string name="partner">partner</string>
    <string name="where_when">Where &amp; When</string>
    <string name="update_progress">(%1$d / %2$d)</string>
    <string name="sync_done">Up to date!</string>
    <string name="sync_error">There was a issue with syncing.\n\nPlease try again later.</string>
    <string name="sync_title">Syncing</string>
    <string name="sync_init">Fetching latest information from server.</string>
    <string name="alert_filter_title">Filter Categories</string>
    <string name="today">Today</string>
    <string name="tomorrow">Tomorrow</string>
    <string name="nav_help_title">Looking for something?</string>
    <string name="nav_help_body">Check out the information section</string>
    <string name="updates">Recent Updates</string>
    <string name="defcon_year">DEFCON 25</string>
    <string name="tutorial_schedule">Filter your schedule to find what you\'re looking for.</string>
    <string name="empty_feed">Couldn\'t find anything.</string>
    <string name="map_day_title">DAY</string>
    <string name="map_night_title">NIGHT</string>
    <string name="notification_text_blank">Starting soon.</string>
    <string name="empty_location">unknown location</string>
    <string name="change_con">Change Conference</string>
    <string name="defcon">DEFCON</string>
    <string name="toorcon">TOORCON</string>
    <string name="shmoocon">SHMOOCON</string>
    <string name="hackwest">HACKWEST</string>
    <string name="layerone">LAYERONE</string>
    <string name="bsidesorl">BSIDES ORLANDO</string>
    <string name="cons">OH SNAP</string>
    <string name="search">Search</string>
    <string name="msg_in_hours">in %1$s hr</string>
    <string name="msg_in_mins">in %1$s min</string>
    <string name="msg_up_to_date">Up to date!</string>
    <string name="error_unable_to_sync">Unable to sync</string>
    <string name="msg_change_con">Change Con</string>
    <string name="msg_change_cons">We\'re branching out to supporting multiple conferences.</string>

    <string name="no_results_for">No results for \"%1$s\"</string>
    <string name="no_results_message">Try expanding your search terms.</string>
    <string name="nothing_to_show">Sorry, nothing to show</string>
    <string name="nothing_here">Nothing here</string>

    <string-array name="nav_item_activity_titles">
        <item>@string/nav_home</item>
        <item>@string/schedule</item>
        <item>@string/map</item>
        <item>@string/information</item>
        <item>@string/partners_vendors</item>
        <item>@string/settings</item>
        <item>@string/change_con</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="cons">
        <item>@string/defcon</item>
        <item>@string/toorcon</item>
        <item>@string/shmoocon</item>
        <item>@string/hackwest</item>
        <item>@string/layerone</item>
        <item>@string/bsidesorl</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="badge_information">
        <item>@string/badges</item>
        <item>@string/badges_description</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="wifi_information">
        <item>@string/wifi</item>
        <item>@string/wifi_description</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="radio_information">
        <item>@string/radio</item>
        <item>@string/radio_text</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="workshop_information">
        <item>@string/workshops</item>
        <item>@string/workshop_info_text</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="location_information">
        <item>@string/where_when</item>
        <item>@string/tut_location</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
